http://www.nmarts.org/privacy.html

Purchase Selection Meeting: Rio RanchoPDF File
New Mexico Arts Commission to Meet Virtually, November 19, 2020
NM Music Commission to Meet Virtually: November 10, 1:00 pm
NM Music Commission to Meet Virtually: Nov 10, AgendaWeb Link
Prospectus Development Meeting: TIME Project New Mexico Historic SitesPDF File
Purchase Selection Meeting: Bloomfield Senior CenterPDF File
Local Selection Committee Meeting: Prospectus #259 Devasthali HallPDF File
Prospectus Development Meeting: TIME Project Las CrucesPDF File
Purchase Selection Meeting: NMSU and NMSU Community CollegesPDF File
Purchase Selection Meeting: Catron CountyPDF File
Purchase Selection Meeting: Curry County Ranchvale Fire DepartmentPDF File
Local Selection Committee Final Selection Meeting: NM Military Institute RoswellPDF File
New Mexico Arts Awards $1.5 Million to Arts Organizations in Need
NM Arts to Distribute $1.5 Million to Arts Organizations in NeedPDF FIle
NM POL State Champ to Take Part in National Recitation Contest in Washington DCPDF File
New Mexico Arts and the City of Santa Fe Seek Designs for Public Art ProjectWeb Link
Nominations Sought for Governor's Awards for Excellence in the ArtsWeb Link
NMAD Rules UpdatePDF File
NMAD Public Rule MeetingPDF File
Press Releases
Home
»
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
[[Wayfinder?&excludeDocs=`128` &ignoreHidden=`true`&level=`3`&startId=`[[UltimateParent? &topLevel=`0`]]`&textOfLinks=`pagetitle`&titleOfLinks=`longtitle`&displayStart=`true`&sortBy=menuindex&sortDir=`ASC`&hideSubMenus=`true
New Mexico Arts Privacy Policy
New Mexico Arts is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to its web sites. As an affiliated web site of the New Mexico Department of Cultural Affairs (DCA), we are governed by the DCA Privacy Policy for ensuring the privacy of all personally identifiable information. This policy ensures that DCA does not collect any personal information about individuals that is not voluntarily submitted by the user. In addition, it ensures that any personal information collected will not be shared intentionally with any third party without having received your prior permission.
For any services or communications which are administered directly by the New Mexico Arts, we will never obtain email addresses from a third party for our subscriber list nor will we collect or share email addresses we obtain through our Web site or any other method (such as registration or membership forms) of obtaining personal information.
Use of Cookies
A cookie is a small file a Web site puts on your computer's hard drive so that the site can remember your preferences or which pages you visited on that site.
As you explore this Web site, it is possible that a session cookie will be set on your computer. A session cookie will tell us which pages you visit and the amount of time between each page visit. This cookie does not remember any information about you or your computer, it just tells us how long visitors spend on our sites and which pages receive the most traffic. A session cookie only remembers information about your current visit to the site. New Mexico Arts uses the information to improve our visitors' experiences on the site. No personal information is ever stored in or obtained from the cookies used on this site.
Please consult the Department of Cultural Affairs Privacy Policy for additional information.
Last modified: January 10 2008 16:33:33.
Links updated: May 22 2018
[[Wayfinder? &startId=`126` &level=`1`]]
© New Mexico Arts, a division of the New Mexico Department of Cultural Affairs.
Bataan Memorial Building, 407 Galisteo Suite 270, Santa Fe, New Mexico 87501
Tel: 505-827-6490 | Instate: 1-800-879-4278 | TTY Relay:1-800-659-8331 | Fax: 505-827-6043
Header Photo Credits from Left to Right
Western New Mexico University, photo by Jay Hemphill WNMU
Karen Yank, "Growing Strength" at Central New Mexico Community College, 2017
Albuquerque Youth Symphony Program, photo by Howard George Photography
Wholly Rags, "Red Earth Dog" by Melissa Larson, at Arte XVIII Stables Gallery, 2018
A Children's Theatre of the Mesilla Valley, photo by Kelly Corkern King
Doña Ana Arts Council, photo by Emmitt Booher
Dancing Earth, artists Shane Montoya, Anne Pesata, Trey Pickett in SEEDS REGENERATION. Location: Abaachi territories, garments by Cheryl's Odom and photo by Paulo T for Dancing Earth
National Dance Institute New Mexico Inc., photo by InSight Foto
This is an HTML5 enabled website. Many pages look best on Chrome or Firefox.
